Hello everyone welcome to this channel.  This video
is related to ICICI Bank Limited.  ICICI
Bank has declared its final dividend for investors along with the release of its March quarter results for the financial year 2025.
How much dividend is ICICI Bank LED paying?
What is the record date for dividend?  And
how has the company's performance been?  You will know the
complete details including pay out record date in this video.
So now let us know in detail about
this dividend and the financial results of the company.
ICICI Bank declared dividend along with
its March quarter results on April 19, 2025.   The
bank said its board has approved a dividend of
₹11 per share to shareholders.  The
bank
said that approval from the shareholders is yet to be taken on this decision.  The
company has not declared the
record date and payment date of this dividend.  The
record date for this dividend will be announced in the Annual General Meeting (
AGM).  ICICI Bank's
standalone net profit
rose nearly 18% to Rs 12,629 crore in the March quarter of FY2025.  The
bank's total income
increased by 14% year-on-year to Rs
49,691 crore from Rs 43,597 crore in the same quarter a year ago.  The
bank's operating expenses increased to ₹
10,788 crore in the March quarter from
₹9,703 crore in the same quarter a year ago.  The bank's
net interest income (NII)
increased by 11% year-on-year to Rs
2,193 crore during this period.  In the March quarter it was Rs 1993
crore.  So far this year, the bank's shares have
risen by about 10%.  The
52 week high of ICICI share
is ₹149 and 52 week low
is ₹151.  Face value of ICICI share is ₹2